unique untranslated 498
- #
- + New Flow
- + New Solution
- ... and {n} more rows
- 1. Describe the product in natural language (specs, ingredients, packaging, certs).
2. Choose input 
- 1. Select text in title, excerpt, or body.
2. Press Ctrl+K (Mac: 鈱楰) to open the floating editor.
3.
- 12M
- 3M
- 3PL
- 6M
- A list of all users including their name, company, email, role, and status.
- AI Applications
- AI Compliance Check
- AI Draft Quotation
- AI Generate Content
- AI Generate Doc
- AI Generating...
- AI Import
- AI Spreadsheet Translation
- AI Translate All
- AI console
- AI features panel coming soon.
- AI generate trade document
- AI generating...
- AI generation failed
- AI generation failed. Try a more detailed description.
- AI import product
- AI quotation draft
- AI revision applied
- AI revision failed 鈥?try rephrasing
